Mss.B.H142.1-3
American Philosophical Society
- Bound volumes, 4.0 4 Letterbooks: 1. June 21, 1750- Dec. 24, 1755 2. June 2, 1750- March 24, 1759 3. March 27, 1759-April 12, 1764 4. May 3, 1764-Nov. 16, 1767 Please use photocopy.; Hall, David, 1714-1772
  - Letterbook, 1759-1764, March 27, 1759-April 12, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Feb. 21, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [Benjamin] Franklin, March 24, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. FILM54-64 FRAME53
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, March 24, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, March 24, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, April 2, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, April 27, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, June 1, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Friendly letter. FILM54-64 FRAME 54
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, June 1, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, June 15, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, June 28, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [Benjamin] Franklin, July 20, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. FILM54-64 FRAME55
    - Letter to Hamilton & Balfour, July 20, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, July 20, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [Benjamin] Franklin, Aug. 24, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. FILM54-64 FRAME56
    - Letter to Hamilton & Balfour, Aug. 24, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Hamilton & Balfour, Sept. 2, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Oct. 22, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Business. Refers to B. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME58
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Oct. 22, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Refers to B. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME 57
    - Letter to [Benjamin] Franklin, Nov. 4, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Friendly letter. Refers to Quincy and W. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME60
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Nov. 4, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Mentions B. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME59
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Nov. 25, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Refers to B. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME62
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Nov. 25, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Business. Refers to B. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME61
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Nov. 25, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Dec. 10, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Dec. 21, 1761; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [Benjamin] Franklin, April 5, May 10, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. FILM54-64 FRAME64
    - Letter to Hamilton & Balfour, May 7, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, May 7, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, May 7, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Concerning B. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME 63
    - Letter to [Hamilton & Balfour], May 10, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, May 10, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, May 10, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 4p. Business. Orders books.
    - Letter to [Benjamin] Franklin, June 9, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Mentions Mrs. Franklin and Sally. FILM54-64 FRAME65
    - Letter to Hamilton & Balfour, June 9, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, June 9, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, June 9, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Orders books.
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, June 12, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L. 1p. Business.
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, June 16, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, July 1, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, July 1, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Aug. 16, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Aug. 16, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Sept. 21, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Sept. 21, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Sept. 28, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Sept. 28, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Hamilton & Balfour, Nov. 1, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Nov. 2, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Arrival of B. Franklin in Philadelphia. FILM54-64 FRAME66
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Nov. 29, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Nov. 29, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William Strahan], Dec. 8, 1762; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, March 3-8, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Feb. 10, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. This letter is crossed off and marked "Mistake."
    - Letter to John Balfour & Co., March 3, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to John Balfour & Co., March 8, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, March 8, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, April 2, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, April 2, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, April 25, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 3p. Business. Orders books.
    - Letter to Balfour & Co., April 26, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, April 27, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, April 27, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, May 14, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 3p. Business. Friendly letter. Orders books for the Library company and others.
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, June 3, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, June 9, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, July 6, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, July 6, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to John Balfour & Co., Oct. 11, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Oct. 11, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Oct. 11, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Business. Orders books for Francis Hopkinson, Library company and others.
    - Letter to [Balfour & Co.], Oct. 27, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [Johnson & Unwin], Oct. 27, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William Strahan], Oct. 27, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Dec. 17, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 5p. Business. Orders books for the Library company and others.
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Dec. 28, 1763; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Business. Refers to Strahan.
    - Letter to William Strahan, March 12, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, March 12, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Alexander Kincaid, March 17, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, April 12, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
  - Letterbook, 1764-1767, May 3, 1764-Nov. 16, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    Letterbook, May 3, 1764- Nov. 16,1767
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, May 3, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p, Business.
    - Letter to W[illia]m Strahan, May 3, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to John Balfour, Edinburgh, May 12, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, May 13, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to W[illia]m Strahan, May 13, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, May 13, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, June 25, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L.S. with initials. 1p. Business.
    - Letter to William Strahan, June 25, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L.S. with initials. 2p. Enc. wanting. Business. Friendly letter. Encloses Franklin's letter to Hogarth. Mentions the Library company FILM54-64 FRAME67
    - Letter to William Strahan, Sept. 3, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Business. Friendly letter. Part of letter in another hand.
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Sept. 3, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L.S. with initials. 1p. Business. Friendly letter. Encloses Franklin's letter to Hogarth. Mentions the Library company.
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Sept. 25, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William Strahan], Sept. 25, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Business. Refers to B. Franklin and the Library company Philadelphia. FILM54-64 FRAME 68
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Oct. 22 - Nov. 7, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Oct. 22 - Nov. 7, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Alexander Kincaid, Nov. 20, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Kincaid & Bell, Nov. 20, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      L.S. 1p. Business.
    - Letter to John Balfour, Nov. 20, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L.S. 1p. Business.
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Nov. 21, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Business. Orders books. Concerning B. Franklin and fonts of type. FILM54-64 FRAME69
    - Letter to David Hall, Philadelphia, Nov. 30, Dec. 6, 1764; Strahan, William, 1715-1785
      London, A.L.S. 3p. and add. End. ----Copy. Friendly business letter. Mentions Dr. Franklin. Ships pictures to Gov. Franklin. Printed in part: R.D. Harlan. "William Strahan..." Lib. Quarterly, XXXI, 243. FILM54-61 FRAME83
    - MARKER DEC 64, 1764
    - Letter to John Balfour, Dec. 20, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L.S. with initials. 2p. Business.
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Dec. 20, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Dec. 20, 1764; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - MARKER 65, 1765
    - Letter to Davie [Hall], 1765; 8" x 12 3/4"; Strahan, William, 1715-1785
      L. 3p. and end. Debates in the Houses of Parliament. (Two portions of the letter are in Strahan's hand.)
    - Letter to Davie [Hall], Feb. 22/March 12 1765; 7 1/4" x 9"; Strahan, William, 1715-1785
      London, A.L.S. 2p. and end. ---- Copy of same letter; with postscript dated March 12, 1765. L. 2p. and end. 7 1/4" x 9" P.S. in Wm. Strahan's hand. FILM54-61 FRAME84
    - Letter to John Balfour, Feb. 25, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Alexander Kincaid, Feb. 25 - March 16, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Johnson & Unwin, Feb. 25, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, March 15, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, March 16, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      L.S. with initials. 2p. Business. Orders books for Mrs. Franklin and others. Concerning B. Franklin's voyage to England. FILM54-64 FRAME 70
    - Letter to Henry Unwin, May 19, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Refers to the Stamp Act.
    - Letter to William Strahan, May 19-23, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L.S. 3p. Business. Trouble with printing news in the colonies. Orders books.
    - Letter to William Strahan, June 13-15, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L.S. with initials. 1p. Business. Refers to stamp act.
    - Letter to [Benjamin] Franklin, June 20, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Stamp act troubles. Friendly letter. Refers to Mrs. Franklin and Sally. FILM54-64 FRAME72
    - Letter to [Henry] Unwin, June 20, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, June 20, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. Business. Concerning fonts of type and B. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME 71
    - Letter to [Benjamin] Franklin, June 22, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Concerning stamp act troubles and Mr. Hughes. FILM54-64 FRAME73
    - Letter to [Henry] Unwin, June 22, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, June 22, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Stamp act troubles. Refers to B. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME74
    - Letter to Davie [Hall], July 8, 1765; 7 1/4" x 9"; Strahan, William, 1715-1785
      London, A.L.S. 4p. ---- Copy of same letter. A.L.S. 3p. and end. FILM54-61 FRAME85
    - Letter to Alex[ande]r Kincaid, July 13, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, July 25, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Henry Unwin, July 25, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Davie [Hall], Aug. 19, 1765; 7 1/4" x 9"; Strahan, William, 1715-1785
      London, A.L.S. 3p. and end: Strahan April 19, 1765. ---- Copy of same letter. L.S (?) 2p. 7 1/4" x 9"
    - Letter to David Hall, Aug. 19 & 23, 1765; 7 1/4" x 9"; Strahan, William, 1715-1785
      London, A.L.S. 1p. and add. Stamp act - plan to avoid paying the duty on advertisements. On same sheet with copy of letter from Strahan to Hall, Aug. 19, 1765.
    - Letter to Henry Unwin, Sept. 6, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Business. Mentions B. Franklin and Strahan. FILM54-64 FRAME 75
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, Sept. 6, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Concerning the stamp act and Hughes. FILM54-64 FRAME77
    - Letter to William Strahan, Sept. 6, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. Business. Stamp act troubles. Mentions B. Franklin and Hughes. FILM54-64 FRAME76
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Sept. 19, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Business. Concerning the stamp act.
    - Letter to David Hall, Oct. 2, 1765; 7 1/4" x 9"; Strahan, William, 1715-1785
      London, A.L.S. 1p. and add. "Copy." Stamp act. Business.
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, Oct. 14, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Concerning the stamp act. FILM54-64 FRAME79
    - Letter to Henry Unwin, Oct. 14, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Refers to B. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME 78
    - Letter to William Strahan, Oct. 14, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Alexander Kincaid, Oct. 14, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William Strahan], Nov. 9, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Friendly letter.
    - Letter to David Hall, Dec. 12, 1765; Library Company of Philadelphia.
      Philadelphia, L.S.: Christopher Marshall, Samuel Ormes, Hudson Emlen, Josiah Hewes. Copy. 1p. Orders books. In Letter from Hall to Strahan; Dec. 16, 1765.
    - Letter to John Balfour, Dec. 16, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Henry Unwin, Dec. 16, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Business. Concerning the stamp act, Franklin and Strahan. FILM54-64 FRAME80
    - Letter to William Strahan, Dec. 16, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 6p. Enc. Business. Stamp act. Orders books for Library company. Sends bill of exchange drawn by Jonathan Williams,sr. Enclosed is copy of letter from the Library company to Hall; Dec. 12, 1765. FILM54-64FRAME 93
    - Letter to Lawrence Holden, Dec. 17, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Alexander Kincaid, Dec. 17, 1765; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - MARKER 66, 1765
    - Letter to James Maggee, Feb. 4, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Orders books.
    - Letter to [Alexander] Kincaid, Feb. 27, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, March 3, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Friendly letter. Business. Concerning Mrs. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME81
    - Letter to William Strahan, March 3, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, April 5, 28, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Refers to the stamp act.
    - Letter to John McAlaster, Hartford, N.C., April 6, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, May 1, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. with initials. 1p. Business. Concerning Mrs. Franklin. Mentions Strahan. FILM54-64 FRAME82
    - Letter to [Daniel Clarke], May 6, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Daniel Clarke, May 7, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, June 7, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 3p. Business. Orders fonts of type. Orders books.
    - Letter to William Strahan, June 12, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, July 7, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, July 12, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Friendly letter. Business. Mentions Mrs. Franklin, Strahan and Sally. FILM54-64 FRAME83
    - Letter to William Strahan, Aug. 19, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Friendly letter. Concerning B. Franklin before the House of Commons. FILM54-64 FRAME85
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, Aug. 19, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Mentions Mrs. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME84
    - Letter to John Balfour, Sept. 20, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Mrs. Elizabeth Unwin and John Bayles, Sept. 20, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Alexander Kincaid, Sept. 20, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Business. Refers to Dr. Shippen.
    - Letter to William Strahan, Sept. 20, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [John] Balfour, Nov. 13, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Alex[ande]r Kincaid, Nov. 13, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Nov. 13 - Dec. 13, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Mrs. Elizabeth Unwin and John Bayles, Nov. 13 - Dec. 13, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Dec. 13, 1766; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 4p. Business. Orders books.
    - Letter to Benjamin Franklin, Jan. 27, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 3p. Business. Concerning a new newspaper sponsored by W. Franklin. Concerning Mrs. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME86
    - Letter to William Strahan, Jan. 31, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [John] Hill, Feb. 6, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 1p. Agrees to handle his medicine.
    - Letter to William Strahan, March 31, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Alexander Kincaid, March 31 - April 4, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Mrs. Elizabeth Unwin and John Bayles, March 31 - April 4, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William Strahan], April 4, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, April 30, May 16-17, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Politics and his, William's, and B. Franklin's role in them. Business. Orders books for Thomas Bond. FILM54-64 FRAME87
    - Letter to John Bayles, May 1 - 17, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to John Bayles, May 16-26, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, May 26, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 2p. Business. Concerning printing for Pennsylvania. Mentions B. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME88
    - Letter to Alexander Kincaid, June 12, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, June 12, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, L. 3p. Business. Concerning trouble between Dickinson and Galloway. Concerning B. Franklin. FILM54-64 FRAME89
    - Letter to William Strahan, July 4, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Business. Friendly letter.
    - Letter to Alexander Kincaid, Sept. 21-26, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to William Strahan, Sept. 21 - Oct. 6, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
      Philadelphia, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. Business. Explains printing in Philadelphia and B. Franklin's role in it. FILM54-64 FRAME90
    - Letter to Bayles & Staples, Sept. 21, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William] Strahan, Oct. 9-17, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to Bayles & Staples, Oct. 17, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to John Hill, Oct. 19, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    - Letter to [William Strahan], Nov. 16, 1767; Hall, David, 1714-1772
  - Account book for work done for the Province of Pennsylvania, Nov. 11, 1756-June 1767; In box labelled Account books (3), 1745-1768; box includes index volume.; Hall, David, 1714-1772
  - Book of bills of exchange remitted to London, Nov. 12, 1745 - Sept. 24, 1752; In box labelled Account books (3), 1745-1768; box includes index volume.; 13x7; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    D. 18p. See table of contents in front of book.
  - Account currant book, 1748-[1768]; In box labelled Account books (3), 1745-1768; box includes index volume.; 13x8-1/2; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    commencing anno 1748[-1768]. D. 67p. Contains account with Benjamin Franklin, among others. For contents, see table of contents in front of volume. Table of contents available. FILM54-64 FRAME 94.
  - Shop book (Account book), April 29, 1767-Sept 7, 1768; In box labelled: "Account book ("Shop book"), 1767-1768."
  - Work book, no. 2, 1759-1766, 1782-1789; B. Franklin and D. Hall (Firm)
    Xerox copy. 89 leaves. From original in the New York Public Library. See: Film 1228 for microfilm. Originally located @ B H142.1f
  - [Receipt book], June 8, 1771 - Oct. 14, 1772; 8" x 4"; Hall, David, 1714-1772
    Ms.D. 7 leaves. Receipts under dates of Oct. 18, 1771, Nov. 29, 1771 and Oct. 14, 1772 are signed by D[eborah] Franklin; that of Nov. 29, 1771 mentions Benjamin Franklin. Bound with: B:H142.3. Originally B H142.2 FILM54-63 FRAME42
  - [Receipt book], Front: June 8,1771-Sept. 4,1776;(Rear) Dec 3, 1771-July 18, 1772; 8-1/4x4-1/4; Two sets of receipts: June 8, 1771-Oct 5, 1776; followed by Nnotes in pencil and some pressed flowers are inter-leaved, named and noted; many blank pages follow; second set of receipts from back cover, Dec. 3, 1771-Jul 18, 1772.; Hall & Sellers.
    D. 1 vol. of 131 leaves of which 64 contain writing. Pertaining to paper making and printing in and around Philadelphia. See index for listing of signatures and people involved. Film 790.1 Table of contents available. Originally B H142.3 Film 790.1
  - Account books (copy 2), 1748-1768; 2.0 Includes Index; Account Currant book, 1748-1768; Account Currant book for printing workd done for Province of Pennslyvania..., 1756-1767. Spine label: "I"
    Xerox copy of account books; spine label [v.] I
  - Letterbooks (copy 2), 1750-1767; Spine label: "II"
    Xerox copy of all four letterbooks; spine label [v.] II